[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Conjunctivitis, referred to as pink eye, is an inflammation of the conjunctiva of the eye. What may be the cause of such inflammation?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Viral infection", "Bacterial infection", "Allergic reaction"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If a TV program is rated G then this is true.", "correct_answer": "It is suitable for all audiences.", "incorrect_answers": ["It contains moderate violence.", "It contains mild sexual situations.", "It is suitable for young children."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of professional does the show producer start dating in The Ugly Truth 2009?", "correct_answer": "Surgeon", "incorrect_answers": ["Lawyer", "Journalist", "Banker"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who portrayed Gabrielle Solis in the TV series Desperate Housewives?", "correct_answer": "Eva Longoria Parker", "incorrect_answers": ["Marcia Cross", "Felicity Huffman", "Teri Hatcher"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Skimmed milk contains riboflavin (vitamin B2), vitamin A and calcium.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This popular police show, which ran from 1951 to 1959, is famous for its very quick paced and to the point dialogue. It starred Jack Webb as police detective Joe Friday, badge#714.", "correct_answer": "Dragnet", "incorrect_answers": ["Los Angeles Precinct", "The Streets of San Francisco", "Men on the Streets"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Godzilla won a Lifetime Achievement Award by MTV in 1996.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does AFK mean in Internet slang?", "correct_answer": "away from computer keyboard", "incorrect_answers": ["almost french kissed", "as far as i know", "all friends are kooks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Botanically speaking, which of the following is not a fruit?", "correct_answer": "Arugula", "incorrect_answers": ["Tomato", "Olive", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the Bible, the very first Rebecca was married to whom?", "correct_answer": "Issac", "incorrect_answers": ["Jacob", "Abraham", "Abel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Freedom of the Seas was the largest cruise ship for 2007. It is owned by Royal Caribbean. Which statement is NOT true about this ship?", "correct_answer": "It is about as tall as the CN Tower.", "incorrect_answers": ["It displaces about 160,000 tons.", "It can carry 3,634 passengers.", "It is about 1,112 feet (340 m) long by 184 feet (56 m) wide."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This film stars Whoopi Goldberg as a singer posing as a nun in order to help out a small convents school choir.", "correct_answer": "Sister Act II: Back in the Habit", "incorrect_answers": ["I Dont Want Nun", "Sister Act", "Divine Secrets of the Ya-Ya Sisterhood"]}]